{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Event-Driven Programming",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": ".NET Assemblies",
    "LastModified": "18 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "06_Handout_1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "These are files that contain compiled code targeted at the .NET Framework.",
      "answer": "Assemblies",
      "choices": [
        "Assemblies",
        "Metadata",
        "Steams",
        "References"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are basically physical packages meant for distributing code",
      "answer": "Assemblies",
      "choices": [
        "Assemblies",
        "Metadata",
        "Steams",
        "References"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is NOT TRUE  about the assemblies",
      "answer": "They are giving a strong, unique name based on the private key cryptography to avoid name collision",
      "choices": [
        "These are files that contain compiled code targeted at the .NET Framework.",
        "These are basically physical packages meant for distributing code",
        "The .NET classes are actually contained in several assemblies",
        "They are giving a strong, unique name based on the private key cryptography to avoid name collision"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are two sections of an assembly.",
      "answer": "Metadata and Manifest",
      "choices": [
        "Metadata and Manifest",
        ".exe and .dll",
        "shared and single",
        "public and private"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are two file extensions of an assembly.",
      "answer": ".exe and .dll",
      "choices": [
        "Metadata and Manifest",
        ".exe and .dll",
        "shared and single",
        "public and private"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It includes information about the data types of the program that are being used.",
      "answer": "medata",
      "choices": [
        "medata",
        "manifest",
        ".exe",
        ".dll"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It holds the information of the assembly, which consists of the name, version number, and the type of mapping information.",
      "answer": "manifest",
      "choices": [
        "medata",
        "manifest",
        ".exe",
        ".dll"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is for standalone applications.",
      "answer": ".exe",
      "choices": [
        "medata",
        "manifest",
        ".exe",
        ".dll"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is for reusable components.",
      "answer": ".dll",
      "choices": [
        "medata",
        "manifest",
        ".exe",
        ".dll"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": ".NET Frameworksâ€™ core assemblies location can be found in _____.",
      "answer": "C:\\Windows\\assembly",
      "choices": [
        "C:\\Windows\\assembly",
        "C:\\Windows32\\assembly",
        "C:\\Program Files\\assembly",
        "C:\\Documents\\assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the simplest type of assembly",
      "answer": "Private Assembly",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It can only be used within a software package that is intended to be used.",
      "answer": "Private Assembly",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It does not require registry entries",
      "answer": "Private Assembly",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Two assemblies with the same class name are not a problem since the application can only see the classes that are mentioned in its assemblies",
      "answer": "Private Assembly",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are libraries that other applications can commonly use.",
      "answer": "Shared Assembly",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Security precautions are necessary when using this assembly since any other software can access an assembly.",
      "answer": "Shared Assembly",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a common problem in shared assembly wherein other classes or variables have the same name that matches with the other shared assembly",
      "answer": "Name Collision",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "A different form of the same assembly might overwrite the shared assembly, and the new version might be incompatible with the existing code.",
      "answer": "Name Collision",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shared assemblies are giving a strong, unique name based on the private key cryptography to avoid name collision.",
      "answer": "Name Collision",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It enables several applications to share shared assembly.",
      "answer": "Global Assembly Cache",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is required to add the assembly to the special directory.",
      "answer": "Global Assembly Cache",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a centralized storage location for .NET Assemblies.",
      "answer": "Global Assembly Cache",
      "choices": [
        "Private Assembly",
        "Name Collision",
        "Global Assembly Cache",
        "Shared Assembly"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which step specifies the statement?<BR>Create a project containing a class file. The class file contains the methods and properties that you want other applications to access.",
      "answer": "Step 1",
      "choices": [
        "Step 1",
        "Step 2",
        "Step 3",
        "Step 4"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which step specifies the statement?<BR>Generate a strong name for the project. The strong name is saved in a strong key filename. The strong key file is created named ShareAssemblyMessageKeyFile.snk and located at the solutions explorer.",
      "answer": "Step 2",
      "choices": [
        "Step 1",
        "Step 2",
        "Step 3",
        "Step 4"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which step specifies the statement?<BR>Specify the key filename in the project by indicating its strong key filename in the AssemblyInfo.cs file.",
      "answer": "Step 3",
      "choices": [
        "Step 1",
        "Step 2",
        "Step 3",
        "Step 4"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which step specifies the statement?<BR>Compile the project to generate an assembly. The assembly is generated with the extension .dll.",
      "answer": "Step 4",
      "choices": [
        "Step 1",
        "Step 2",
        "Step 3",
        "Step 4"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is not a step in creating a shared assembly?",
      "answer": "Create a project containing a stream file. The class file contains the methods and properties that you want other applications to access.",
      "choices": [
        "Create a project containing a stream file. The class file contains the methods and properties that you want other applications to access.",
        "Generate a strong name for the project. The strong name is saved in a strong key filename. The strong key file is created named ShareAssemblyMessageKeyFile.snk and\r\nlocated at the solutions explorer",
        "Specify the key filename in the project by indicating its strong key filename in the AssemblyInfo.cs file",
        "Compile the project to generate an assembly. The assembly is generated with the extension .dll"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    }
  ]
}
